Police
Let's chase our dreams...
... holding hearts burning...
... like the summer sunshine.
If we have courage...
... at 100 miles an hour...
... I'm sure the door will open.
Since sadness is the road
that leads to smiles...
... dull, dingy shoes will
start to shine, too.
The most wonderful dream
in the world...
The pounding beat speeds up.
The eyes are prisms that
catch the wind...
... and in the voices of
countless friends...
... I feel happiness.
AND SO THEY MET
As of this moment, fifteen minutes
late already, I see...
I'll go for it.
Let it slide! Please!
I guess not, after all.
In that case...
Whew...
She couldn't have chased
me this far.
N... No way...
Police
It ain't fair if all that counts is speed!
I'm gonna get caught!
A temple?!
My lucky day!
Charge!
Go! Go!
I'm impressed. But it looks like
she's reached her limit.
Heave! Heave! Heave-HO!
NATSUMI POWER BOOST ON!
DASH! Left-right! Left-right!
Eh?!
Fine!
In hopes that I can do well
at my new workplace.
Oshou! Oshou! You sure are
lively, considering the heat.
Note: "Oshou:" in Buddhism, the priest in charge of a temple.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm in a hurry, so I'll
catch you later!
Whew! I thought I was a goner.
What's the time?
Nine... Wha?
There! Hey, kitty, that was pretty
dangerous, you know!
Even though you're lucky
it was me passing by...
...you were on the verge of becoming
today's first accident fatality! Hmm?
Oh! You're hungry,
huh? OK, OK...
Huh? What?!
Gone... It's gone...
My lunch... My lunch!
And now, the question;
How many moving violations
did you commit?
Score
Use of an area prohibited to motor traffic.
Changing lanes in a no-passing zone.
Disobeying traffic signs.
Disregarding instructions of an officer.
And... exceeding the speed limit, too.
Suspension of License
The posted legal speed is 30 kph, so
that puts you 25 kph over...
...but in deference to kitty,
I'll let it slide.
So if you would kindly
sign here...
...Ms. Natsumi Tsujimoto!
Huh? How do you
know my name?
Welcome to Bokuto Precinct!
Bokuto Police Station
Natsumi Tsujimoto!
Yes, sir!
As of today, you are a policewoman
of Bokuto Precinct. Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
And on your first day of duty, you're
an hour and ten minutes late.
Incorrect, sir.
Hmm?
An hour and twelve
minutes, sir.
That's some nerve
you've got.
People say that to me
all the time, sir!
In any case, if you have an
excuse, I'll hear it. Well?
Yes, sir, I do!
The truth is, today, I actually got the
fried egg for lunch done really well.
And when I went to give it to the old lady
next door, she was so psyched!
She went on about how I just had
to become her grandson's bride.
But her grandson is
still only seven...
...so she gave me lots of pickled
vegetables by way of thanks...
...and I was re-soaking them when
I looked at my watch...
...and suddenly it was
eight o'clock!
I raced like mad to get myself together,
and when I got on my RZ...
...wouldn't you know it, the
engine wouldn't turn over!
And it was just fine
yesterday, too!
But that's A-OK! I have a Moto-Compo,
y'know! And it's in top condition!
If I really pushed it, I'd be on time!
Am I lucky or what?!
But I wasn't going to
get off that easily!
No sooner did I hit Mito Boulevard,
then, of all things!
Pun on "Mito Koomon," a famous TV samurai.
You ran into Lord Koomon's entourage, I presume?
Eh? Oh, wow. Making a joke that
far off must be a kind of genius, sir!
And?
At any rate, I, Natsumi Tsujimoto, was
late, but I will give my all for my duty.
In the name of love, courage, and justice,
I will protect the people! That is all!
All right! Welcome aboard!
Oh, thank you.
My fellow officers, I, Natsumi Tsujimoto...
...hope that we will work
well together. Huh?
As she says. I want you all to help
her out wherever necessary.
Kobayakawa, come
here for a sec.
Yes, sir.
This is Miyuki Kobayakawa. She too was
just assigned here this past spring.
Starting today, she will
be your partner.
Miyuki Kobayakawa.
How do you do?
Partner?!
You've got real nerve.
I like that.
Here we go...
I'm getting to like it here, too.
It looks like this is a happening
place, and it feels right to me.
I like the way you talk. I'm Ken
Nakajima, motorcycle patrol.
People call me the "White Hawk
of Bokuto." How do you!
Nakajima, Yoriko, I have some things
to do, so take over for me, OK?
Oh, I'll fix those binoculars
for you. Later...
Uh, yeah...
You see, Nakajima
has a thing for...
I can hear you, Yoriko.
Oops!
There's too much you don't
know, Nakajima.
Sorry.
There seems to be
a lot to remember.
Oh, excuse me for a sec. I've got to talk
about something. With my partner.
Hey! What're you doing
to my bike?
You wiped out pretty
badly this morning!
The kickstarter was broken, and
you were leaking oil, too!
Oh, I put in new wires
and plugs.
Give it proper maintenance
from now on, OK?
And I tinkered around with
various other things too...
...but this time it's a special
job, on the house.
Oh! I'm so lucky!
...NOT! I mean, what's the big idea,
checking up on a person like that?
How much do you
know about me?
Let's see, career history,
special skills...
...and performance evaluations from your
previous postings... as of now, that is.
Is that all? Then you don't know about
when I was in school, and...
...I worked my butt off to support
my motorbike hobby...
...or that in school I was known
as the queen of tardiness...
...and the eating monster...
Ah, I see, I see.
I'll put that in your data file.
Why are you going over my background
like that? What am I to you?
My partner, of course.
What're you looking
at, Nakajima?
The birds. I'm bird watching.
Oh? Birds are wearing uniforms
these days, eh?
Wh... What are you talking
about, Yoriko?!
It's not like I'm interested
in Kobaya!
Aw, you're too easy to trip up, Nakajima.
It's just no fun at all.
Do me a favor, and don't spread
any weird rumors, OK?
I'm the tough guy, after all...
The tough guy, huh?
Starting today, we'll be in charge of the
area from Districts Three through Five.
Two patrols a day, in the morning
and in the evening.
In summertime, we work 'til six.
Oh, and by the way...
...the basement cafeteria's "A" Lunch is
full of oysters, so that'd be my pick.
I don't care for oysters.
Oh, really?
That and...
...a certain someone
right in front of me.
I know it's rude, but
I'm gonna be blunt.
I don't think I can make
this work out with you.
You're the type that gets picky about
data this and data that...
...you crack down on traffic violations
like there was no tomorrow...
...and to top it off, you meddle
in other people's affairs.
You're completely
unlike me.
Yeah, there may be no guarantees that
we'll become really good partners.
But there is just one thing that I can
say with certainty; I'm really...
...l'm really starting to like you.
OK, then, let's do this...
I'll toss this coin. If it comes up
tails, we'll talk to the Captain...
...and have ourselves reassigned.
If it comes up heads...
...I team up with you, huh?
Our future... is in my hands...
What was that?
Hold it, you!
Let's go after him, too!
Fine by me!
Captain! A red Mini is racing through
the area! It's terrible!
A red Mini...
Nakajima, Kobayakawa, and
Tsujimoto are chasing it.
We've got to send out backup!
Don't worry about it.
Huh?
There'll be no danger from that
red Mini. We can let it be.
Uh... yes, sir.
You come along whenever
someone new shows up...
Nice going! You took that corner
like nobody's business!
But it looks like you're
out of luck.
There's construction work up
ahead. It's a dead end!
That was rude!
Sand!
Nakajima!
Are you all right, Nakajima?
Just putting on a little show!
Now get after him!
Uh... right.
I'm counting on you two.
You bastard!
You were waiting for
us? What a jerk!
Unforgivable...
Huh?
I built that GSX-R specially... And
you go and make it wipe out...
I'll get you if it's the
last thing I do!
Fox calling Kittens.
Fox? Who is this?
The game has begun.
It's the driver
of that Mini!
In 120 minutes, fireworks
will go off at H8K2.
Fireworks? You
can't mean!
Is he talking about
a time bomb?
Let's synchronize watches.
3... 2... 1...
Hey! What the heck's H8K2?
You will know that when all
the running around is over.
What're you after?
This is a salute to the establishment
of your new partnership.
How do you know
about that?
Besides, we still haven't decided
whether to BE partners!
This is a game. Let's
enjoy ourselves!
If you like, you can even
call for backup.
If you lack confidence
in yourselves, that is.
"Catch me by yourselves,"
is that it?
You're on! We'll catch you long
before those two hours are up!
Then I wish you luck.
Don't lose him!
I know, I know!
He's heading for
the riverbed!
Hold on tight, OK?
What is it with that Mini?
It's an ERA Turbo.
From the outside, it's just a Mini
that's been modified a little.
But it's a whole different
beast on the inside.
What do you mean?
I mean we're dealing with
a serious car nut.
Then we can't beat him?
Don't worry! This car's
no slouch, either!
Wha?
I've modified the Beat-type E-074
engine into a twin-cam type...
...and upped the displacement
to 700cc.
And with the turbo and
intercooler systems...
...the maximum engine output exceeds
100 hp. And on top of that...
"On top of that?"
There's a custom-made
nitro injector, too!
"Nitro?!"
Nitro! On!
We're gonna catch you!
You tell people not to speed,
but just look at you!
If they run, I chase them.
It's my job, after all.
You're all right.
You're not getting away!
Damn! Y... You're good!
Now's our chance!
Huh?
There's a high school up ahead.
The road takes a big detour.
If we play our cards right, we
can catch him in a pincer!
Which means it's time for
this baby's entrance.
Let's do it!
This baby's smoking! She
really is something!
Now I'm set!
Coming through!
And... take that!
Nice shot, sweetie!
Checkmate! The game
is over, Mr. Fox!
This area is closed to traffic.
My condolences!
You can't get away now!
Give yourself up!
WHAT?!
N... Natsumi! Get him!
I'm on it!
Only thirty minutes left.
It's all over, I guess.
The game of tag ends here.
You both did well. As a reward,
I'll give you a hint.
The code name of your goal is "Emily."
Study your information once more.
Give it everything you've got.
That is all.
"Emily?" A girl?
What did he mean by that? I'm
no good at this kind of thing!
Calm down, Miyuki.
Try to remember...
He said we'd understand when all
the running around was done...
When all the running
around was done...
That's it!
Have you figured
something out?
Look! I've drawn a line through
the roads we chased him over.
Isn't this... an airplane?
Serial number H8K2, code name "Emily,"
refers to the Type Two Flying Boat.
Built in 1940, it was tops in the world
during WWll when it came to...
...speed, flight range, and waterborne
takeoffs and landings!
What's that got to do
with anything?
There still is one now...
at Odaiba Park.
Only twenty minutes to go!
We'll never make it using normal
roads. Find us a short cut!
OK!
There's a subway tunnel under
construction 500m ahead!
If we cut through there, it puts us directly
on Expressway Nine... the Bayshore!
Roger!
Ten minutes!
We gotta make it!
There it is... by the landing gear!
Everyone! Please evacuate!
This is dangerous! Please evacuate!
They said it's dangerous!
Hurry! Please get out of here!
Only thirty seconds left!
Look, you get out of here, too!
Huh?
I can defuse this old thing.
So get out of here!
Miyuki! Even for you, it's impossible!
I'll throw this thing in the ocean!
That's impossible, too!
How many meters do you think
it is to the ocean from here?
You can't throw it that far!
Look, let me handle it!
Get your hands out of the way!
We're running out of time!
Time?
Wow! That's pretty!
Fireworks?
Game over ♥
From Fox to Kittens
If found, please report to police.
"Game over. If found, please
report to the police?"
Oh! I just bet!
It is! It's my lunch! I'm happy!
Oh, is that all?
How green.
We went through a lot today... but
didn't it seem pretty interesting...
...when all's said and done?
Well, it wasn't boring,
that's for sure...
Hmph. You certainly looked like you
were enjoying yourself, though.
Yes, ma'am. Thanks to my top notch
partner, it was an enjoyable day.
Now that's more like it.
Hey, Partner, are you interested
in moving?
Moving?
Your present apartment is far away
and inconvenient, right?
There's a nice place, very close
to Bokuto Precinct.
Lots of sunshine, and a pretty,
punctual roommate, to boot.
Are you by any chance suggesting
we live together?
You'd benefit by not being
late anymore.
What's your real motive?
It's kinda unsafe for a woman
to be living alone, you know!
What does that make me?
My bodyguard!
Oh, no! And I've still got
lunch left over, too!
Okay, say ah!
Ah!
Salty! What is this?
W... Why you...
By the way, what was the outcome
of that coin toss?
Oh! I completely forgot.
Let me do it.
Sure. I'll leave it up to you.
Thank you.
OK then, here I go.
Be my guest.
How about THIS?!
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
... I will protect you from sighs.
The sunset skyline flashes past
in my side-view mirror.
This is the road I drive on every day,
believing in my dreams.
On rainy days, windy days, and days
when I wanted to throw it all away...
... you smiled as you
sat beside me.
I love the unchanging vista, the sky
that we watch together.
That's why I'm confident that I can
hang in there, if it's for you.
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
... I will protect you from sighs.
I love this town where we
happened to meet...
It's coming... it's coming...
There's a storm coming!
S... So you're the type that gets excited
when a typhoon comes too, huh?
Oh, brother!
Well, of course! Water flooding,
storms thrashing...
...trees falling along streets, people
crashing into windows!
Streets without people!
Slippery roads!
And with things flying all over, danger
everywhere, it's such a joy!
Er... hello?
You're Under Arrest, File 2,
"Tokyo Typhoon Rally."
TOKYO TYPHOON RALLY
Looks like there're others
just like you!